for you guys this session is what is
对你们来说，这次会议是什么
cool in Java 8 and new in Java 9 if we
如果我们在Java 8中很酷，在Java 9中又很新
have time at the end I'll show you a
最后有时间，我会告诉你一个
couple of demos
几个演示
if not we'll make do with all of the
如果没有，我们将尽一切努力
content in the slide so standard
幻灯片中的内容如此标准
disclaimer when I talk about what's in 9
当我谈论9中的内容时免责声明
these are our current plans such subject
这些是我们目前计划的主题
to change so it's not a promise it's
改变，所以这不是一个承诺，而是
just the current plans ok don't write a
只是目前的计划好，不要写
contract based on that about myself I'm
基于关于我自己的合同
a director of product management with
产品管理总监
the Java platform group with Oracle I've
我与Oracle的Java平台组
been in charge of the JDK since joining
自加入以来一直负责JDK
Oracle through the Senate position so I
甲骨文通过参议院职位使我
was one of those guys that join bulk in
是那些大量加入的人之一
2010 before that I worked at Sun
2010年之前，我在Sun工作
Microsystems support management for in
微系统支持管理
the Java team as well not directly with
Java团队也不是直接与
the JDK at the time and before that I
当时和之前的JDK
worked a little bit in Florida I got an
在佛罗里达工作了一点
MBA from MIT and a systems engineering
麻省理工学院的MBA和系统工程
degree from University aneema in case my
如果发生我的大学灌肠学位
name didn't give it away it wasn't
名字没有放弃它不是
really from here so first the first part
真的从这里开始所以第一部分
is Java 8 one of the biggest updates
是Java 8的最大更新之一
ever to a major language at the time the
曾经是主要语言
editor of dr. Dobbs this one is actually
博士编辑多布斯这个实际上是
the one thing that I'm most proud of
我最骄傲的一件事
that was part of the team that came out
那是团队的一部分
with JDK 8 now that's the current
现在使用JDK 8
version of the JDK and I'm going to give
版本的JDK，我将给出
you a very rich content how many people
你一个非常丰富的内容有多少人
here are developers good I'm in the
这是我在的开发人员好
right conference so how many people here
正确的会议，所以这里有多少人
are using Java 8 ok most seven
正在使用Java 8好的，最多七个
six five four three two don't be ashamed
六五四三二不要以为耻
there's one of you out there now okay so
现在有一个人在那里，所以
for those of you that are used in Java 7
对于那些在Java 7中使用过的人
or later these will be new for the guys
或以后这些将是新的
that are using Java 8 I imagine you'll
使用Java 8我想你会
see the part of eight anybody here has
看到这里有八个人的一部分
tried JDK nine early access and why not
尝试了JDK九种早期访问方式，为什么不这样做
you first we'll go through it so let me
你首先我们会经历它，所以让我
tell you a little bit about JDK 8 and
告诉你一些有关JDK 8和
there's a lot more than this but you
还有很多，但是你
know these are the most interesting
知道这些是最有趣的
parts of it land expressions
部分土地表达
default methods method references and a
默认方法，方法引用和
little overview of the day time API and
白天API的简要概述和
then I'll just give you the eye chart X
那我就给你视力表X
for all of the other features so that
所有其他功能，以便
you can go and find more about it the
你可以去找到更多关于它的
first part anybody here programs with
第一部分任何与这里进行编程的人
JavaScript or Ruby or Python ok so
JavaScript，Ruby或Python可以
you're familiar with lambda expressions
您熟悉lambda表达式
right the idea is that you can pass data
正确的想法是您可以传递数据
I'm sorry you can pass behavior around
抱歉您可以通过行为
as you can pass data so everybody's
因为您可以传递数据，所以每个人的
familiar with the concept of I have a
熟悉我的概念
variable I'm going to put a number in
变量，我要在其中输入一个数字
there number is data the idea of lambda
有数据就是lambda的想法
expressions is I can do the same with
表达式是我可以做到的
behavior not just data but behavior now
行为不仅是数据，还包括现在的行为
so as an example this is using the new
例如，这是使用新
enhanced for-loop right if I wanted to
如果我想增强循环功能
remove everybody in a collection that
删除集合中的所有人
it's greater than 18 and looking for you
大于18并在寻找您
know like only the people under 18 how
像只有18岁以下的人一样知道
would I remove it using this construct
我会使用此构造将其删除吗
in the enhanced for-loop operator I do
在增强的for循环运算符中
not have any method for calling it out
没有任何方法可以调出
so if I wanted to try this right this is
所以如果我想尝试这个权利，这是
I'm just going to show you a little bit
我只是给你看一点
how the lambda how lambdas change the
Lambda如何改变
way we design API so if I wanted to do
设计API的方式，所以如果我想做
this I would actually have to go and
我实际上必须去
switch back to the long form that was
切换回原来的长格式
available before JDK 5 where I use an
在使用我的JDK 5之前可用
iterator and that's because I need the
迭代器，这是因为我需要
iterators remove button so I just added
迭代器删除按钮，所以我刚刚添加了
a lot of boilerplate in order to be able
很多样板才能
to just remove some
只是删除一些
for my collection right there's a better
对我的收藏来说，有一个更好的选择
way but until JDK 8 it was really hard
但直到JDK 8之前，这真的很难
to do this the right way
以正确的方式做到这一点
ideally what we would like is for there
理想情况下，我们想要的是那里
to be some sort of interface that would
成为某种可以
allow me to pass on behavior and then
让我传递行为，然后
for the designers of the collections to
对于集合的设计师
provide a virtual method called remove
提供一个称为remove的虚拟方法
if ok and remove a footwork by passing
如果可以，请通过
in a collection and passing it the
在一个集合中并通过
predicate so what am I going to do and
predicate，那么我该怎么办，
it would magically go to the collection
它会神奇地去收集
and remove everybody now we could have
并删除我们现在可以拥有的所有人
created this in JDK 7 but it would have
是在JDK 7中创建的，但是
been very painful to use because the
使用起来非常痛苦，因为
only way for passing this behavior you
通过这种行为的唯一方法
know here's the collection people a
知道这里是收集人
bunch of people people and then I would
一堆人，然后我会
have to have written all of this
必须写所有这些
boilerplate to pass that functionality
通过该功能的样板
and that's a lot of code for something
这是很多东西的代码
very simple so the reality is we didn't
非常简单，现实是我们没有
the person that wrote the collection API
编写集合API的人
didn't feel that this was something that
不觉得这是
everybody was going to use and therefore
每个人都将使用，因此
the collection 80 I didn't have a remove
我没有删除的收藏集80
if now everything in green here it's
如果现在这里所有的东西都是绿色的
really boilerplate using lambdas you can
真正使用lambdas的样板，你可以
rewrite this I guess right remove people
重写这个我猜对了删除人
then for every person here's the
那么对于每个人来说
operation right gauge greater than 18 so
操作权规大于18
if this is true and you're going to do
如果这是真的，你将要做
it for everybody
每个人都可以
remove them from the collection right so
从集合中删除它们，这样
now you can pass behavior right what am
现在你可以通过行为
I going to do with each one of them as
我将与他们每个人做
before I could pass data now this is not
在我可以传递数据之前，这不是
just about trying to make the code look
只是试图使代码看起来
smaller let's show a little bit of a
让我们来展示一下
more complicated example right anybody
任何人都可以使用更复杂的示例
what does this code do just by looking
这段代码只是通过查看来做什么
at it quickly
快点
it finds amongst the people in my
它在我的人中找到
collection only from the male's the
仅从男性收集
highest weight it will throw away the
最高的重量会扔掉
you know like the females right it takes
你知道像女性一样
a little bit of you know reading to get
你们中的一些人知道阅读
that right and if you notice I'm not
那个权利，如果你注意到我不是
just telling you what to do I'm telling
只是告诉你我该怎么办
you in which order to do it I'm telling
你告诉我按照什么顺序去做
the collection iterate one person at a
集合在一个位置迭代一个人
time right get the gender get the way
正确的时间让性别变得正确
get the max now we can do this using
得到最大值，我们可以使用
lambdas something that looks a little
lambdas看起来有点像的东西
bit more like the problem statement
有点像问题陈述
right get the list of people filter out
正确地将人员列表过滤掉
everybody you know just filter the male
你认识的每个人都过滤男性
and then map you have you heard the
然后在地图上听到
expression Map Reduce this is the map
表达式Map缩小这是地图
part right I've got a bunch of people I
一部分，我有一堆人
need to map it to something and I'm
需要将其映射到某个东西，我是
saying go and look at that wait in this
说去看看那个等待
case I could have looked at the age
我本来可以看年龄的
whatever right so that's the map part
没关系，那是地图的一部分
and then I'm going to reduce it and say
然后我要减少它并说
at now instead of having a collection of
现在而不是收集
people I'm going to have a collection of
我将要收集的人
weights after the mapping I'm going to
映射后的权重
reduce it by saying just give me the max
说只给我最大就减少它
okay now it's prettier to look at but
好吧，现在看起来还不错
the truth is if this was all we were
事实是，如果这就是我们
going to get out of lambda expressions
要摆脱lambda表达式
it was a lot of work to be done in here
在这里要做很多工作
we wouldn't have done it just for that
我们不会仅仅为此而做
what makes it more interesting is what
是什么使得它更有趣？
happens if you want to rewrite this
如果您要重写此事件
because this is still going sequentially
因为这仍然依序进行
one person at a time and do this
一次一个人做
sequentially what if you want to write
顺序地，如果你想写
this in parallel so that if you have a
这是并行的，所以如果你有一个
bunch of different processors you could
一堆不同的处理器，你可以
have some processors handle half of the
让某些处理器处理一半的
collection on the other processor JDK 7
其他处理器JDK 7上的collection
we introduced something called the fork
我们介绍了一种叫做叉子的东西
join framework which would pretty much
加入框架，这差不多
allow you to do that
允许你那样做
you would get a problem you would say
你会说一个问题
I'm going to chunk it into smaller
我要把它切成小块
pieces and I'm going to let each
件，我要让每个
processor or you know handle part of it
处理器，或者您知道要处理它的一部分
and what if I wanted to do this thing in
而如果我想在
parallel using the for game framework
使用for游戏框架并行
the fork joint framework
叉关节框架
that you're not supposed to read that
你不应该读那个
it's just to show you the amount of
只是为了告诉你
boilerplate the stuff in red is actually
样板里红色的东西实际上是
how you solve the problem
您如何解决问题
everything else is the forging framework
其他一切都是锻造框架
now it's not always better to use
现在使用它并不总是更好
parallelism you will pay some price for
并行性，您将为此付出一些代价
this so in many cases the question is
所以在很多情况下，问题是
should I do it or not well you know try
我应该做还是不做，你知道尝试
it out measure the response and see
衡量响应，看看
which one is better
哪一个更好
how many people do you think are willing
你认为有多少人愿意
to write all of this and we'll get it
写下所有这些，我们会得到的
right in order to discover that you know
为了发现你知道
what it was easier to do it sequentially
顺序执行比较容易
you know it's small enough of a
你知道它足够小
collection nobody right now if you go
如果你去的话，现在没有人收藏
back for a little example wouldn't it be
回到一个小例子，不是吗
great if the people in that D api's
如果那个D api里的人很棒
handled that for impart for you so let's
为您传授知识，所以让我们
convert this one into the parallel
将此转换为并行
version done okay
版本完成了
rather than streams I did parallel
而不是我并行执行的流
streams it may look by the way like this
流可能看起来像这样
is traversing through the collection
正在遍历集合
three times one for filtering one for
三遍一滤
mapping one producing this is much
映射一个产生这个的很多
better than that you'll do it all in a
比这更好的事
single pass so it's only hitting the
单次通过，所以只击中了
collection once it's very efficient so
收集一次非常有效，所以
that's a little bit of what lambda
那就是lambda的一点点
expressions do for you we introduced
表达式为您服务我们介绍了
these in JDK 8 and it has changed the
这些在JDK 8中已经改变了
way that we code quite a bit it also
我们编写代码的方式也很多
introduced a couple of interesting
介绍了几个有趣的
situations right so that was lambda
情况正确，所以那是lambda
expressions now default methods have you
表达式现在是默认方法了
remember do you remember the API called
记得你还记得API叫
Nile it's called new IO right and that's
尼罗河被称为新IO权利，那就是
because we had an IO a new input output
因为我们有一个IO一个新的输入输出
interface and then somebody came up with
界面，然后有人想出了
some improvements to it and we had then
对其进行了一些改进，然后
to create a new set of api's for that
为此创建一个新的API集
called new IO we had a bunch of
称为新IO，我们有一堆
collections now we want to add this new
现在，我们要添加此新收藏
abilities like the remove f4h statement
诸如删除f4h语句之类的功能
how would you feel if we tell you yeah
如果我们告诉你，你会感觉如何
here's a new set of collections
这是一组新的收藏
collections - right
集合-对
because all the other collections they
因为所有其他收藏
didn't have these new capabilities and
没有这些新功能，
you already code it for them and in in
您已经为他们编写了代码
Java we wouldn't let you modify a
Java，我们不允许您修改
collection by adding a new method right
通过添加一个新的方法收集权利
that would have been a problem I really
那真的是个问题
didn't want to see another new
不想看到另一个新的
collections API so we introduced another
集合API，因此我们引入了另一个
interesting concept called default
有趣的概念称为默认
methods you see here we say stream right
您在这里看到的方法我们说正确的流
collections that didn't have stream in
没有流的收藏
JDK 7 so how can collections have stream
JDK 7集合如何流化
now what if you've created your own
现在，如果您创建了自己的
collections and you didn't implement
集合而您没有实现
stream I'm not going to break your code
流，我不会破坏您的代码
here's what we did when you define the
这是我们在定义
collection interface now you can pass a
收集界面现在您可以通过
default method and the beauty of this is
默认方法，这的好处是
if you do implement the method right
如果您确实实现了该方法
what you've implemented will be what is
您实施的将是什么
used but if somebody doesn't implement
使用过，但是如果有人没有实现
the method they get one for free this is
他们免费获得一个的方法是
like the public defender you know if you
像公设辩护人，你知道你是否
cannot afford an implementation one will
付不起实施的意愿
be provided to you free of charge and
免费提供给您
this allowed us to create some methods
这使我们可以创建一些方法
on collections that already existed and
在已经存在的收藏上
therefore you can continue using your
因此您可以继续使用
collections they magically get new
他们神奇地获得新的收藏
methods you don't have to choose for new
您不必为新方法选择的方法
collections okay so that's major plus
可以，所以这是主要的优点
for a decade we did it of course in the
十年来，我们当然是在
API you can do it on your own code as
API，您可以在自己的代码上执行
well
好
we also now allowed studying method in
我们现在还允许在
interfaces okay so static methods you
接口还可以，所以您可以使用静态方法
can have zero or more static and another
可以有零个或多个静态数
one that I like is the method references
我喜欢的一种是方法引用
there's a bunch of lambda expressions
有很多lambda表达式
that look like this I'm going to get a
看起来像这样，我会得到一个
particular variable and I'm just going
特定的变量，我就去
to call one method in the variable right
在变量右边调用一个方法
so p-p get name we this is so common and
所以pp取名，这很常见，
when we were doing JDK 8 we didn't just
当我们做JDK 8时，我们不仅
create these new methods we went and we
创建我们去过的这些新方法，我们
use them in the jdk libraries itself so
在jdk库本身中使用它们，因此
before it even was Reese we had a major
甚至在里斯还没来得及
use case with you know hundreds and
你知道用例数百
thousands of lines of code where we
数千行代码
thought oh let's use this method and we
以为哦，让我们使用这种方法，我们
discovered this was pretty common so
发现这很普遍，所以
there's a shorthand for it now if you
如果你现在有一个简写
see this little double column operator
看到这个小小的双列运算符
it's the same thing right it's just go
这是同一件事，就走了
and call to uppercase and that's Method
然后调用大写字母，那就是Method
references you will see that probably
引用，您可能会发现
when you start looking into JDK 8 code
当您开始研究JDK 8代码时
now you know what it is
现在你知道它是什么
right it's just shorthand for the second
对，这只是第二个的简写
one so in summary lambdas are just
总之，lambda是一个
functions these has allow us to create
这些功能使我们能够创建
new api's and now we can use functional
新的api，现在我们可以使用功能了
interfaces we've introduced default
我们引入的接口默认
methods and method references now that's
方法和方法参考现在
for the technical part for the practical
对于实用的技术部分
part you know I work with NetBeans most
您知道我最常使用NetBeans的部分
I des have some sort of tool that will
我会用某种工具
allow you to automatically convert your
让您自动转换您的
code so that it uses new land
代码，以便它使用新的土地
expressions where for example you were
表达式，例如您所在的位置
using anonymous inner classes so this is
使用匿名内部类，所以这是
what it looks like in that means if you
看起来是什么意思，如果你
just here's an anonymous inner class and
这是一个匿名的内部类，
I'll say use lambda expression poof
我会说使用lambda表达po
we'll convert it so if you're new to
我们将对其进行转换，如果您是新手，
these what I would recommend is go to
这些我推荐的是
some code that you wrote and that you
您编写的一些代码
understand let the tool find some
了解让工具找到一些
instances where it can convert what you
它可以转换您的内容的实例
wrote to lambda expressions and then
写给lambda表达式，然后
look at it before next to the conversion
在转换之前先看一下
and at least it took me I don't know
至少花了我我不知道
three or four days of going through
经过三四天
these before it click and I started
这些在点击之前，我开始
writing lambdas myself directly rather
我自己直接写lambda
than using any tools to help me and it's
而不是使用任何工具来帮助我，
easier to do it with code that you are
使用您自己的代码更容易做到
familiar with so that you are not
熟悉，这样你就不会
wondering what is it doing and you just
想知道它在做什么，而你只是
look into the syntax and how it changes
研究语法及其变化
so here's another one
所以这是另一个
use member references so you see this
使用成员引用，所以您会看到
one it looks a little bit like what I
一个看起来有点像我
explained that little member reference
解释说小会员参考
and it turns it into get a real count so
它变成了真正的计数，所以
many tools allow even for batch
许多工具甚至允许批处理
refactoring so instead of just going one
重构，而不是仅仅重构
file at a time you can just go and say
一次提交文件就可以说
here's my project could you check the
这是我的项目，您可以检查一下
syntax and make sure that it's using
语法，并确保它正在使用
everything in JDK format and it'll give
JDK格式的所有内容，它将给
you a little before-and-after for each
你们每个人前后
one of them so that's pretty useful okay
其中之一，所以非常有用
I recommend that you don't just blindly
我建议你不要盲目地
accept things understand them because
接受事物了解他们，因为
that's the whole point you want to write
这就是你要写的重点
these this way from now on okay so as I
从现在开始这样的方式
said a rich content that's it for
说的是丰富的内容
lambdas now I'm going to talk about one
lambdas现在我要谈一个
of my other favorite expressions daytime
白天我最喜欢的表情
API
API
these are 3:10 I believe Stephen Colburn
这些是3:10，我相信Stephen Colburn
this is one of those api's that was not
这是那些不是
developed by Oracle anybody here heard
由Oracle开发的任何人都可以在这里听到
of Java time right and before that Java
Java时间的权宜之计
had its own set of API now there's
现在有自己的API集
nothing wrong with the previous API but
以前的API没什么问题，但是
they don't let you assume anything so a
他们不会让你承担任何责任
couple of questions anybody knows
任何人都知道的几个问题
whether we're using the Gregorian or the
无论我们使用公历还是
Julian calendar anybody
朱利安历法
okay I'm not gonna put you in a spot
好吧，我不会把你放在一个地方
we're using the Gregorian calendar
我们正在使用公历
nowadays next question what's the
如今的下一个问题是什么
difference between those two
两者之间的区别
Gregorian and Julian anybody yeah in the
格里高利安和朱利安有人在
Julian calendar the rule is every four
朱利安历法则是每四个
years you get a leap year okay that's
年，你会有get年，那就是
the old one the new one has a little
旧的新的有一点
rule that says except in the years that
规则说，除了那几年
are divisible over 100 in which case
在这种情况下可以被100整除
they're only live years if they're also
如果他们还活着，那么他们只能活几年
divisible over 400 and the final
可除以400，最后
question who thinks a developer should
问谁认为开发人员应该
know that before deciding which calendar
在确定哪个日历之前要知道
to use because the previous API sort of
之所以使用，是因为以前的API
assumed that you're going to have to
假设您将不得不
answer all these questions right it also
也回答所有这些问题吧
didn't let you get away with anything
没有让你逃脱任何事情
like ignoring time zones if you wanted
喜欢忽略时区
to specify a time you would have to tell
指定您必须告诉的时间
me a time zone it wouldn't accept
我不接受的时区
anything by default and we humans
默认情况下任何东西，我们人类
actually are much more comfortable with
其实更舒服
a little leeway right and most of our
有一点回旋余地，我们大多数人
problems don't need that level of detail
问题不需要那么详细
so show the time and now this new date
所以显示时间和现在这个新日期
and time it's much more intuitive it's
时间更直观了
closer to the way we think about date
更接近我们思考日期的方式
and times so here we go we replace date
和时间，所以我们去替换日期
calendar time zone and date format it's
日历时区和日期格式
now fluent in mutable thread-safe
现在精通可变线程安全
and pretty easy to use if you've been
如果您曾经
using Java time this will look very
使用Java时间，这看起来非常
familiar it's the same guy that did the
熟悉这是做过的同一个人
both of them you can look him up and
他们两个都可以仰望他，
he'll explain why he thinks this is the
他会解释为什么他认为这是
next level of evolution so there's some
进化的下一阶段，所以有一些
tweaks that he didn't do any other time
调整他没有其他时间
that he pulled out in here strong typing
他在这里强力打字
easy formatting and parsing and it's
易于格式化和解析，它的
interoperable so if we were using
互操作性，所以如果我们使用
calendar date you can just toggle back
您可以切换回日历日期
and forth units fields and chronologies
来回单位字段和时间顺序
he'll explain those and support some
他会解释这些并支持一些
regional calendars it has a bunch of
它有很多的区域日历
calendars built in if we have time I'll
如果有时间，我会内置日历
give you a little demo of you know a
给你一些演示，你知道
cool instance of that and it uses ISO
很酷的实例，它使用ISO
8601 and for those that don't care for
8601和那些不关心的人
the numbers that's the normal calendar
正常日历的数字
that way but I use is nowadays so you
这样，但我现在使用的是
have a range of types dates consisting
有一系列类型的日期，包括
of year month and day that's when
每年的年月日
don't care about time right like local
像当地人一样不在乎时间
date local time let's just the time and
日期当地时间让我们只是时间和
if you combine them together there's
如果您将它们组合在一起，
another type called local daytime which
另一种称为本地白天的类型
looks pretty much like you join those
看起来很像你加入那些
two together pretty convenient the time
两个在一起的时间很方便
zones are handled separately okay and
区域分别处理好吗，
there's the instantaneous point in time
有瞬时的时间点
instants which is the closest thing that
瞬间是最接近的事物
we have to the previous java.util date
我们必须到以前的java.util日期
now choose the correct date and time
现在选择正确的日期和时间
when designing an application okay local
在设计应用程序时可以在本地进行
date stores in year month date most of
日期存储在年月日期中的大多数
these will use the Gregorian calendar
这些将使用公历
the one that we know one use most of the
我们知道的一种使用了大部分
time so things like birthdays start
时间，例如生日开始
these holiday days when somebody asks
这些假期，有人问
you your birthday you usually follow up
你你的生日，你通常会跟进
with where in the world where you born
在你出生的地方
so that they can you know tell you happy
让他们知道你告诉你快乐
birthday at 7 p.m. because that's when
晚上7点生日，因为那是
the times now you just care for the date
现在的时间，你只是在乎日期
right local tanning just the time
恰到好处的时间在当地晒黑
there's no date in here so opening hours
这里没有日期，所以营业时间
on the laptop
在笔记本电脑上
wake me up at 6:30 which they every day
他们每天在6:30叫醒我
ok and the local daytime you just glue
好吧，在当地的白天，你只是胶水
them together you have instant the best
他们在一起，你瞬间得到最好的
thing for login time cutting and then
减少登录时间，然后
you have time zones now the time zones
您现在有时区时区
as you will know the world divided into
如您所知，世界分为
different time zones and it's not
不同的时区，不是
mathematical we change the rules on when
数学上，我们会在何时更改规则
you have daylight saving times and they
你有夏令时，他们
even change within the same country
甚至在同一个国家内变化
based on rules made up by people on the
根据人们在
spot they change year over year so if
发现它们一年一年变化，所以如果
you can avoid them and work only with
您可以避免使用它们，而只能与
local times and safe like that Europe
欧洲这样的当地时间和安全地带
your life will be much simpler if you
如果你的生活会简单得多
can store everything say in universal
可以将所有内容说成是通用的
time and then convert them only to
时间，然后仅将它们转换为
output or input much simpler try to do
输出或输入要简单得多的尝试
that we do have time zone information so
我们确实有时区信息
if you need these you have four classes
如果你需要这些，你有四个班级
the song ID that's the one that has a
带有编号的歌曲ID
little text that you're familiar with in
您熟悉的小文字
the offset that tells you five - five
告诉您五到五的偏移量
hours we're here - eight or - seven
我们在这里的几个小时-八个或七个
depending on the time of the year and
根据一年中的时间而定
some rules that will tell you when to
一些规则可以告诉您何时
switch from one to another and Sunday
从一个切换到另一个和星期日
time is the one where you keep all of
时间是你保留所有的时间
this now calendar systems main classes
现在这个日历系统的主要类别
use the ISO calendar system which
使用ISO日历系统
matches the Gregorian one which is the
匹配公历之一
one that we use nowadays not
我们今天不使用的一种
historically accurate I don't know if
历史上准确我不知道
you know that you know we switched from
你知道你知道我们从
the Julian calendar to the Gregorian and
儒略历到公历和
different countries did it at different
不同国家的做法不同
times there was some offset so some
时候有一些抵消，所以一些
dates don't actually exist if you look
如果您看，日期实际上并不存在
them up okay
他们起来好吗
and there's other calendars also
还有其他日历
supported here app which is a lunar
支持这里的应用程序，这是一个农历
calendar and actually one of my favorite
日历，实际上是我最喜欢的日历之一
ones for a particular application that
用于特定应用的
I'll show in a minute
我等一下
Japanese Mingo Thai Buddhist as far as I
就我而言，日本民俗泰国佛教徒
can tell the big difference between
可以分辨出
these last three is they're the same as
这最后三个是相同的
ours only they have a different year and
我们只有他们有不同的年份，
that's a gross oversimplification so
这太过简单了
somebody can you know cares to educate
你知道有人在乎教育吗
me later that's fine the hidden one is a
我待会儿没事，隐藏的是
lot more interesting my mind that's a
更有趣的是我的想法
lunar calendar okay and it only affects
农历好吗，它只会影响
dates not times of course you have
日期当然不是你的时间
durations sometimes you don't want to
持续时间有时你不想
specify a start and end you just want to
指定您只想开始和结束
say a duration so three minutes and I
说持续三分钟，我
don't want to say starting now and any
不想说从现在开始
three minutes from now it's just three
从现在三分钟到三分钟
minutes
分钟
you know without a beginning and end and
你知道没有起点和终点，
you have well the duration is you can
你有持续时间是可以的
think of it as hours and minutes right
认为它是正确的小时和分钟
it's pre exact then you have the period
这是确切的，那么你有一个时期
which is a little bit more complicated
这有点复杂
that's that's remember when I said that
那就是当我说
we people are very comfortable with a
我们人们对
little bit of ambiguity with dates and
与日期和
times years month and day and my example
年月日日和我的榜样
of this one is if I tell you it's one
如果我告诉你这是一个
month away how many days is that well
一个月走了好几天
depends right it could be 28 30 or 31
取决于可能是28 30或31
and we're okay with that so if you know
我们对此表示满意，如果您知道
if you're working at that level you can
如果您在该级别上工作，则可以
use a period if you want more
如果您想要更多，请使用一段时间
granularity use the
粒度使用
this one right so for those of you
这个权利适合你们
taking pictures this is the one that has
拍照这是有
everything so local date local time both
一切都如此当地日期当地时间
of them together sewn day time at the
他们一起缝制白天的时间
times on the instant duration and period
即时持续时间和期间的时间
and as I promised that was a very
正如我所承诺的那样，
average content we have a lot of changes
平均内容我们有很多变化
in JDK 8 and you can go and find
在JDK 8中，您可以找到
information about any of these changes
有关任何这些更改的信息
and by the way this piece itself is a
顺便说一句，这块本身是一个
shorter list right now what I've shown
我现在显示的简短列表
you here you can find in a lot more
您在这里可以找到更多
detail if you want to go into the Java 8
如果要使用Java 8，请查看详细信息
launch event so I hate URLs because
启动事件，所以我讨厌网址，因为
nobody remembers them so instead I'll
没有人记得他们，所以我会
tell you what to look for if you go into
告诉你要去找什么
your search engine and type Java 8
您的搜索引擎，然后键入Java 8
launch you will find the expert that
启动您会发现专家
worked on those libraries on those api's
在那些api的那些库上工作
on lamda explaining them in a lot more
在lamda上解释了更多
detail than I ever could so if you want
比我以往任何时候都更细致
to learn more these are the people to
要了解更多这些是人们
look into right Brian gets to our marks
看看正确的布莱恩达到我们的目标
Steven Colver
史蒂文·科弗
now that's the summary for my favorite
现在，这是我最喜欢的摘要
features in JDK 8 now let's look a
现在让我们看一下JDK 8中的功能
little bit into the future coming in JDK
JDK的未来发展
9 there's over 90 jep's Java and has
9有超过90个jep的Java，并且
been proposals that are targeted and are
是针对性的提案，
actually ready in the early access
早就准备好了
builds of JDK 9 this is a public page
JDK 9的构建，这是一个公共页面
just search for open JDK 9 you will find
只需搜索打开的JDK 9，您就会发现
the schedule and down here the complete
时间表和这里完整的
list
清单
now nobody that you know doesn't work on
现在，您认识的任何人都无法正常工作
this has ever read the complete listing
这曾经读过完整的清单
details so I'll just pick and choose
详细信息，所以我就选择
some of them and I've categorized them
其中一些，我已经将其分类
into behind-the-scenes improvements new
进行幕后改进新
features new standards housekeeping and
提供新标准的客房清洁服务和
some stuff that it's gone no longer
一些已经消失的东西
available in JDK 9 so behind the scenes
在JDK 9中可用，因此在幕后
these are the goodies that you get just
这些是你得到的好东西
by moving to JDK 9 you don't have to
通过迁移到JDK 9，您不必
recompile your code you can just grab
重新编译代码即可
your classes compiled on JDK 8 run them
您在JDK 8上编译的类将运行它们
on JDK 9 and you get some freebies write
在JDK 9上，您会得到一些免费赠品
some performance improvements less
一些性能改进较少
memory etc
记忆等
so I'm not going to go into a lot of
所以我不会过多地讨论
detail because the intention here is
细节，因为这里的意图是
I'll just give you a glimpse if you want
如果您愿意，我会给您一瞥
to know more and I failed to mention
知道更多，我没有提及
that one here is the little URL thingy
那个是那个小URL
just type the jet number here and you'll
只需在此处输入飞机号，您就会
get a lot more detail
获得更多细节
okay so store in turn strings in CDs
好的，因此将字符串依次存储在CD中
archive short of it is you can have a
存档不足的是，您可以拥有一个
bunch of strings shared the same
一串弦共享相同
representation memory so it uses less
表示内存，因此使用较少
memory saved a lot of memory from our
内存为我们节省了很多内存
tests in Oracle products that manage a
管理产品的Oracle产品中的测试
lot of strings even better compacts
很多弦甚至更好的紧凑
strings we realized that we could do
我们意识到我们可以做的字符串
better than saving everything in in in
胜于将所有内容保存在
four bits we could do 16 bits I'm sorry
四位，我们可以做16位，对不起
in 4 bytes we could do usually 16 bits
在4个字节中，我们通常可以做16位
and if needed we can go larger but the
如果需要，我们可以做得更大，但是
majority of strings take now about half
现在大多数弦大约占一半
as much space okay now this one I love
现在有足够的空间好吗，我爱这个
it because it only took 20 years for
因为它只花了20年
Java doc to get a little search box so
Java文档获得一个小的搜索框，因此
your documentation created with Java doc
您使用Java doc创建的文档
will now have that search capability by
现在将具有该搜索功能
default and that's a pretty good search
默认，这是一个很好的搜索
if I do say so myself even though you
即使我自己也这么说
can search camelcase
可以搜索驼峰
and we'll do a smart hit it will not
我们会做一个明智的选择
just find everything alphabetically and
只需按字母顺序查找所有内容，
put it in there but it's uncanny how the
把它放在那里，但真是不可思议
talk here is more likely than not the
在这里说话更有可能
one that you want it okay so that's what
一个你想要的就可以了
you get for free we also have a bunch of
您免费获得，我们也有一堆
improvement that these are new tools and
改进这些是新工具
capabilities that like most things right
最喜欢的功能
if you don't use them you don't get the
如果您不使用它们，您将不会得到
value of it but they're available for
它的价值，但它们可用于
you if you're now calling again to JDK 9
如果您现在再次调用JDK 9
these are the ones that are most likely
这些是最有可能的
to be used by most developers there's a
可供大多数开发人员使用
bunch of other smaller ones that are
一堆其他较小的
pretty obscure first one project Dixon
相当模糊的第一个项目Dixon
and I'm going to go into a little bit
我会讲一点
more detail if anybody goes to any call
如果有人去打个电话，可以得到更多细节
any session about JDK 9 this is what
关于JDK 9的任何会议都是
you'll see
你会看到的
right we've modularized that platform
是的，我们已经将该平台模块化
now most of the work was to modularize
现在大部分的工作是模块化
the jdk itself but of course you can use
jdk本身，但是您当然可以使用
that to modularize your own applications
模块化您自己的应用程序
and this makes managing large code bases
这使得管理大型代码库
much simpler okay there's another side
简单多了，还有另一面
story this is a partial you know this is
故事这是局部的，你知道这是
just a zooming of the graph that
只是图的缩放
explains the module so you have the base
解释模块，以便您有基础
system depends you know then you have
系统取决于你知道然后你有
modules that depend on base it's
取决于基础的模块
actually here here's Mason ago I cannot
其实这里是梅森，我不能
even read it here so with this
甚至在这里读到这个
modularization allow us to create this
模块化允许我们创建这个
other one of my favorite tools j-link
我最喜欢的其他工具之一j-link
the java linker so up to now the common
Java链接器到目前为止
deployment mode model is every Java
部署模式模型是每一个Java
program shares one GRE write so all
程序共享一个GRE写入，因此全部
programs run on the same runtime and
程序在相同的运行时上运行
that means that your GRE even though you
这意味着即使你
may want it to run only just a very
可能希望它只运行一个
small program that doesn't use a lot of
不使用很多的小程序
the classes that are available in the
可用的类
JRE that Jerry contains everything right
JRE认为Jerry包含所有正确的内容
it contains core bar encryption and if
它包含核心条加密，如果
you want to do a little hello world why
你想做一个小小的世界你为什么
do you want to have all of those
你想拥有所有这些吗
capabilities now it's a lot more common
功能现在变得更加普遍
to have an application include its own
具有自己的应用程序
runtime right
运行权
this model of let's all share a runtime
我们的这个模型共享一个运行时
it comes from the time where 50
它来自50
megabytes was a huge load and nobody
兆字节是一个巨大的负载，没有人
wanted to carry another 50 megabytes
想再携带50兆字节
right now how many of you have little
现在你们有多少人很少
applications on your phone that are
手机上的应用程序
measured in gigabytes so the idea of we
以GB为单位，因此我们的想法
must all share a runtime to save a few
必须全部共享一个运行时以节省一些
megabytes it's no longer the most
不再是最大的兆字节
current one with j-link
当前的一个j-link
we've introduced an optional
我们介绍了一个可选的
intermediate step which is you normally
中间步骤，通常是你
we're compiling your code and then you
我们正在编译您的代码，然后您
were running it right jaelyn you can
在正确运行jaelyn，您可以
link it and you can also use it to
链接它，您也可以使用它来
create a customized runtime so we'll
创建一个自定义的运行时，所以我们将
basically go and say what modules that
基本上去说什么模块
your application need oh it only needs
您的应用程序需要哦，它只需要
base
基础
login and this other module okay rather
登录和其他模块还可以
than having the whole thing in there let
而不是把整个东西放在那里
me create a special image just for you
我为你打造一个特殊的形象
with those three modules and therefore
与这三个模块，因此
you'll be smaller a lot faster you can
您可以更快地变小很多
include your own modules into this image
在此图像中包含您自己的模块
so I can then give you here's a runtime
所以我可以给你一个运行时
and it has everything that you need to
它具有您需要的一切
run your Java program and it's a half or
运行您的Java程序，它的一半或
a third of the size of a full GRE so if
完整GRE大小的三分之一，所以如果
you're creating a bunch of containers
您正在创建一堆容器
and trying to create runtimes for a
并尝试为
particular application as opposed to
特定的应用而不是
something that will run every
东西会跑
conceivable Java program you really need
您真正需要的可能的Java程序
to look into this okay enhance
研究这个可以增强的功能
deprecation anybody what said why do we
贬低任何人说我们为什么
deprecated API we thought of something
过时的API，我们想到了一些东西
better than that one there was something
比那个更好的东西
wrong with the previous one we have to
与上一个错误，我们必须
get it out of there or the style wasn't
把它弄出来或者风格不是
right we actually use deprecation for
对，我们实际上将折旧用于
many things and it was very confusing
很多事情，这非常令人困惑
because to me the important thing about
因为对我来说重要的是
the application is are you going to
该应用程序是你要
throw this API away because if you're
丢弃此API，因为如果您
going to remove it I want to know about
要删除它我想知道
it
它
right there are other cases on which
在其他情况下
something new and better is available
有新的更好的东西可用
which means if I'm coding a new program
这意味着如果我正在编码一个新程序
I should use that but if I have an old
我应该使用它，但是如果我有一个旧的
program that works fine I don't need to
程序运行正常，我不需要
go and refactor it right it's going to
去重构它是正确的
work fine since we were overloading the
工作正常，因为我们超载了
term deprecation to mean any of those it
术语“弃用”是指其中的任何一个
was very useful with JDK 9 we've added
在我们添加的JDK 9中非常有用
an annotation and the important one here
注释和重要的注释
is condemned equals true and the idea is
被谴责等于真实，想法是
to tell you we intend to remove this API
告诉您我们打算删除此API
in the next version so if you're using
在下一版本中，如果您使用的是
an API that has condemned equals true
被谴责的API等于true
you know today that it is not likely
你今天知道这不太可能
going to work in the next version of the
将在下一个版本的
JDK ok even though the next version of
即使下一个版本的JDK也可以
the JDK hasn't even started you already
JDK甚至还没有开始
know that now you can get a warning when
知道现在您可以在收到警告时
you compile but we also provide you a
您编译，但我们也为您提供
tool that's the set up the red bullet at
这是设置红色项目符号的工具
the second one it's called Jade upper
第二个叫做翡翠鞋面
scan you can run it on
扫描你可以运行它
any code and will tell you whether it's
任何代码，并会告诉您是否
using any deprecated API and you can
使用任何不推荐使用的API，您可以
pass it a parameter and say just show me
传递一个参数，然后说给我看
the ones that are about to be removed so
即将被删除的
that's very useful you don't need to
这是非常有用的，您不需要
have the source code you can just run it
有源代码，您可以直接运行它
on the microf who here has created small
在microf上谁创造了小
collections right it's even worse if
对吧，如果情况更糟
you're trying to create something that's
您正在尝试创建一些
immutable because I don't know if you
一成不变，因为我不知道你是否
discover how to do it you have to first
发现如何做，你必须先
create it then populate it one at a time
创建它，然后一次填充一次
and then convert it to immutable that's
然后将其转换为不可变的
a little bit too much molar plate for
磨牙板有点太多
something that small with this one you
这个东西很小，你
can do it in a single go so most of them
一口气就能做到，所以大多数人
they have an overload so I think it's up
他们有超负荷，所以我认为
to ten elements yes so you can do up to
十个元素是的，所以你可以做到
ten elements with these factory
这些工厂的十个要素
collections okay
收集还可以
pretty nice J shell anybody knows this
不错的J Shell，任何人都知道
guy rebel other languages have had these
盖伊叛军其他语言有这些
tools for a while so if you want to
工具一会儿，所以如果你想
explore an API right now what do you do
立即探索API，您该怎么做
you fire up NetBeans or tapes you create
启动NetBeans或创建的磁带
a little scaffolding right because if I
一点脚手架，因为如果我
want to know how an API works I'm going
想知道我将如何使用API
to need to create a method that uses
需要创建一个使用
that API right so I'm going to have to
该API是正确的，所以我将不得不
use one of those you know main that
用那些你知道的主要
calls this little thing just to discover
称这个小东西只是为了发现
how the API works that's way too much
API的工作方式太多了
trouble
麻烦
so IDs actually have integrated this
所以ID实际上已经集成了
tool into itself I said I use NetBeans
工具本身，我说我使用NetBeans
there's an early access build of
有一个早期访问版本
NetBeans that works with JDK 9 and if we
适用于JDK 9的NetBeans
finish quickly I'll show you a little
快点完成，我会告诉你一点
example of how to use this rebel tool to
如何使用此反叛工具的示例
play around you can just open a command
玩转就可以打开命令
line you can type it has code completion
行，您可以键入它具有代码完成
it's a little bit simplified you don't
有点简化，你不用
have to put the semicolon at the end of
必须将分号放在
every statement you can export you can
您可以导出的每个语句都可以
you know have a little Java interface
你知道有一点Java接口
come up and you can edit what you've
出现，您可以编辑自己的内容
used so it's pretty useful for
使用过，因此对于
exploratory code and once you understood
探索性代码，一旦您理解
how it works you can just go ahead and
如何运作，您可以继续
write the write API without having to
无需编写写API
play around with it
玩它
something that I wish we had before move
我希望我们在搬家之前有一些东西
to release jar files so what happens
释放jar文件，那么会发生什么
when we come up with a great new idea in
当我们提出一个很棒的新主意时
JDK 9 but you want your same code to
JDK 9，但您希望使用相同的代码
work on JDK 9 &amp; 8 &amp; 7 you're pretty much
在JDK 9＆8＆7上工作，您几乎可以
stuck because you know what I cannot use
卡住是因为您知道我无法使用
this new API because what happens when
这个新的API，因为当
somebody tries to run it on JDK 8 it's
有人试图在JDK 8上运行它
going to blow up in their face and
要炸毁他们的脸，
therefore there are some things that
因此，有些事情
don't get adopted as quickly as they
不要像他们一样被尽快采纳
could be because developers have this
可能是因为开发人员有这个
concern about I don't want to have to
担心我不想
create a version for aid and a version
创建一个援助版本和一个版本
for 9 I want a single version that works
9我想要一个可以使用的版本
across both of them now here's how this
现在这两个人都这样
looks like JDK 8 and if you're running
看起来像JDK 8，如果您正在运行
this particular jar in JDK 8 or below
JDK 8或更低版本中的特定jar
these are the classes ABCD if you're
这些是ABCD类别，如果您
running it in JDK 9 it's going to
在JDK 9中运行它
override a and it's going to use this
覆盖a，它将使用它
one instead and B this one instead so
一个代替B这个代替
these two classes a class and B class
这两个班是A班和B班
down here can use nine only API the a
在这里只能使用九个API
and B class is up here those are the
B班上课了
ones that you write for eight and below
你写的八岁及以下
and the idea is that as we move forward
想法是随着我们前进
and you have this available you can have
你有这个可以
different classes and say this one is
不同的班级，说这是
four eight nine and ten this one is
四八九十十这个是
roughly and you can have in a single jar
大概可以放在一个罐子里
a program that runs in different
以不同方式运行的程序
versions of Java okay some new standards
Java版本可以使用一些新标准
these are things that we didn't invent
这些是我们没有发明的东西
they're just we're grabbing what's
他们只是我们在抢什么
available elsewhere Unicode eight so you
在其他地方可用Unicode八，因此您
can see every version of Java adopts new
可以看到每个Java版本都采用了新的
versions of Unicode I beat you have a
我打败你的Unicode版本
seven launched with unicode six so
七个与unicode一起启动六个所以
there's about 10,000 new symbols anybody
大约有10,000个新符号
care to guess what the vast majority of
猜猜绝大多数
those are emoji cyclists alike but if
那些都是表情符号骑手，但是如果
you were dying to write Navajo in lower
你很想写较低的那瓦伙族人
case you're going to need Unicode 8
如果您需要Unicode 8
because that's where it was introduced
因为那是它引入的地方
before that you were always screaming
在那之前，你总是在尖叫
when you're writing in Navajo I had to
当您在纳瓦霍写作时，我不得不
look that up because you can write your
查一下，因为你可以写你的
your property files now you can use
您的财产文件，现在您可以使用
utf-8 so when you pair it with the other
utf-8，所以当您将其与另一个配对时
one you can have a property file that's
一个你可以有一个属性文件是
all ammaji
所有阿玛吉
if you know you are so inclined okay you
如果你知道你很喜欢你
before that you could do it but you have
在那之前你可以做到，但是你有
to encode them now you can actually use
现在可以对它们进行编码了
utf-8 so that's pretty nice OC speed all
utf-8，所以OC速度相当不错
CSP stapling for pls that's a mouthful
CSP装订很麻烦
that's one of my favorite features it's
这是我最喜欢的功能之一
pretty technical but I love it here
非常技术，但是我在这里喜欢
anybody knows what that is good I get to
任何人都知道我能得到的好处
show off right now when you go on you
继续前进时马上炫耀
ping a server right imagine that you try
对服务器执行ping操作，请想象您尝试
to connect to an API that says I'm going
连接到说我要去的API
to connect to I don't know Microsoft the
连接到我不知道微软的
way it works is you go and you connect
它的工作方式是您去连接
to Microsoft and Microsoft replies and
微软和微软的回复以及
says HTTP here's a certificate issued by
说HTTP这是由
Verisign that says I am Microsoft so
威瑞信说我是微软，所以
what does your computer do it says when
您的计算机说什么时候
was the last time that we check the
这是我们最后一次检查
certificates that were revoked from
被撤销的证书
Verisign was it more than an hour ago
威瑞信是一个多小时前
no it's less than an hour okay let me go
不，不到一个小时，好吧，我走
check that list yeah that certificate is
检查该列表，是的，证书是
not there we're good if it's more than
如果不是，那我们就好了
one hour of this is the first thing you
这一个小时是你的第一件事
check you have to go on Ping very time
检查您是否必须继续使用Ping
and say has that certificate been
并说那个证书是
revoked right and that means that a lot
撤销权利，这意味着很多
of people are paying in first Microsoft
的人正在使用第一台Microsoft付款
and then Verisign there's even a
然后Verisign甚至还有一个
theoretical denial of service attack
理论上的拒绝服务攻击
where you use a certificate that has
您使用的证书具有
been revoked and you block the person
被撤销，您阻止了此人
from being in Verisign right and most
远离Verisign的权利
browsers now they assume that if they
浏览器现在他们假设，如果他们
cannot think very sad you know there's
不能认为很难过，你知道
connection problems everything is
连接问题一切都在
probably okay very good let's just rest
可能很好，很好，让我们休息
it right it also allows you to leak a
它也可以让您泄漏
little information Verisign has an idea
很少的信息Verisign有一个想法
so how many people are visiting
那么有多少人来
Microsoft because they're getting
微软，因为他们越来越
pinging so how does this work
ping，这如何工作
Microsoft once an hour things very
微软每小时一次的事情很
silences could you give me a signed note
沉默，你能给我签个字条吗
saying that I'm not expired and rather
说我没有过期，而是
than every client having to being very
比每个客户都必须非常
time remember how you were going to
时间记得你打算如何
trust the answer for a sign for one hour
相信答案一个小时
this is no different the only difference
这没什么不同，唯一的区别
is now Microsoft says here's my
现在微软说这是我的
certificate and here's a recent
证书，这是最近的
signature less than one hour old saying
签名不到一小时的俗语
that I'm not expired you don't have to
我没有过期，你不必
check anything else pretty neat huh
检查其他的东西很整洁吧
new hash algorithms
新的哈希算法
who here has kept abreast of all the
谁跟上了所有
news about md5 and sha-1 they're all
有关md5和sha-1的新闻，它们都是
getting hacked that means you need new
被黑客入侵意味着您需要新的
ones so you know we're going to continue
那些，所以你知道我们将继续
in this little hamster wheel for as long
在这个小仓鼠轮子上
as I can think I don't see any answer
我可以认为我没有任何答案
now so they'll keep cracking and we'll
现在，他们将继续努力，我们将
keep adding html5 Java doc just looks
继续添加html5 Java文档
better so here's another one HTTP - so
更好，所以这里是另一个HTTP-所以
this is protocol it's you know very used
这是协议，您知道非常习惯
nowadays it makes things appear to load
如今，它使事情看起来像加载
faster there's a whole set of tricks
更快，有很多技巧
that they use - even though it's sending
他们使用的-即使它正在发送
them as same amount of information
它们与相同数量的信息
things appear to load quicker now this
事情现在似乎加载更快
one also allows me to introduce
一个也让我介绍
something new called incubator modules
新的东西叫做孵化器模块
now what is that you may ask how about a
现在你可能会问什么
nest oh no come on play with me what is
窝哦，不要和我一起玩是什么
that so incubator modules is when we
所以孵化器模块是当我们
define an API and we put it in this
定义一个API，我们把它放在
standard the minute that we put it out
标准我们放出的时间
there somebody goes and builds a huge
有人去建造一个巨大的
system on it and then we cannot change
系统就可以了
it ever again so whenever there is
再一次，所以只要有
something that we're not quite sure if
我们不太确定是否
the API is ready we always have this
API已经准备好了，我们总是有这个
problem right we try to ask for feedback
问题权，我们尝试寻求反馈
but until it's actually in the JDK most
但直到它实际上在JDK中
people don't get feedback incubator
人们没有得到反馈孵化器
modules are it's a set of modules that
模块是一组模块
pretty much guarantees that that API
几乎可以保证该API
will not be there in the next version ok
在下一个版本中不会出现
so you can go and play with it but it
所以你可以去玩，但是它
comes with a warning
带有警告
you shall not build something on top of
你不应该在
these that you intend to use in
您打算在其中使用的这些
production for the long run
长期生产
because it will not be there in the next
因为它不会在下一个
version hopefully it will help as though
版本希望它将有所帮助
by getting some more feedback and we can
通过获取更多反馈，我们可以
make sure that the API when it gets into
确保API进入时
this standard is the right API okay now
这个标准是正确的API，现在可以了
housekeeping we've set up some future
家政服务，我们已经建立了一些未来
improvements and we reduce some
改进，我们减少了一些
complexity this one is the one that's
这是一个复杂的
going to get the most news we've
将获得我们拥有的最新消息
encapsulated most internal API now I can
现在我可以封装大多数内部API
find you on 1998 web page you can look
在1998年的网页上可以找到您
in the you know Internet Archive with
在您知道的Internet存档中
Sun Microsystems telling its develop
Sun Microsystems讲述其发展
first do not use the internal API
首先不要使用内部API
they're not part of the specification
它们不是规范的一部分
that's what we use internally to
这就是我们内部使用的
implement the specification so stay away
实施规范，所以远离
from those they may change the may
从他们可能改变的可能
disappear and you know it's if you're
消失了，你知道这是如果你是
using some other vendors implementation
使用其他供应商实施
of Java they may not be there now when
的Java他们可能现在不在那里
we did this we of course have access to
我们这样做了，我们当然可以使用
the same open source repository that
相同的开源资源库
everybody has we went a look to a bunch
大家都去看了一堆
of commonly used libraries how many
常用库的数量
people think you know that less than
人们以为你知道不到
half of them but you know about half of
他们一半，但你知道一半
them use this internal API
他们使用此内部API
half of them anybody know 60 80 90
他们一半人都知道60 80 90
percent how many do you think actually
你实际认为多少
use internal API is even though we told
即使我们告诉使用内部API
them not to try a hundred percent okay
他们不要尝试百分百好吧
every non-trivial API that we defined
我们定义的每个平凡的API
they use some of these internal API that
他们使用了一些内部API
makes your code brittle and it makes
使您的代码易碎，并且使
those internal API you know we cannot
您知道我们无法使用的那些内部API
really evolve them so we really can and
真正地发展它们，因此我们可以并且
we're finally going to encapsulate them
我们最终要封装它们
they're not going to be there by default
他们默认不会在那里
okay
好的
now that means that those common
现在，这意味着那些常见的
libraries that I was talking about
我正在谈论的图书馆
there's going to be a new version of
将会有一个新版本的
them that doesn't use those internal API
他们不使用那些内部API
there's also escape clause there is a
还有逃逸条款
command line that you can pass to expose
您可以传递以暴露的命令行
one of these api's back if you need it
这些api之一，如果需要的话
please don't do that unless you're
请不要这样做，除非你是
planning to rewrite your code and this
打算重写您的代码
is just a temporary step okay there's a
只是一个临时步骤，好吧
handful of API that when we went looking
少数API，当我们去寻找
we decided you know what these are not
我们决定你知道这些不是
just convenient things these actually do
这些实际所做的只是方便的事情
important things and there is no actual
重要的事情，没有实际的
real you know supporting API part of the
真正的您知道支持API的一部分
specification that can do what these
可以做到这些的规范
things do so for the ones listed there
那里列出的人这样做
and only those they will remain enabled
只有那些将保持启用状态
by default you don't have to pass
默认情况下，您不必通过
anything those will remain there we're
任何那些都将留在那里
working very hard to provide some api
非常努力地提供一些API
that are part of the spec that do the
是规范的一部分，
things that these guys did
这些家伙所做的事情
in a supportive way until we do they
以支持的方式，直到我们做到
remain available this is not we've
保持可用这不是我们
turned them into part of the
把它们变成了一部分
specification and now that now they're
规范，现在他们
there forever
永远存在
hopefully in JDK 10 or JDK 11 or as soon
希望在JDK 10或JDK 11中或尽快
as we can app with a new replacement
因为我们可以用新的替代品来应用
those will disappear but for nine don't
那些会消失，但九个不会
they need to use them if you have to
他们需要使用它们
okay there is a tool that's available
好的，有一个可用的工具
since JDK 8 called Java dependencies J
自从JDK 8被称为Java依赖J
depth that you can run against by code
您可以通过代码运行的深度
and it will tell you whether you're
它会告诉您您是否
using this API so I would recommend that
使用这个API，所以我建议
you go ahead and run it against your
你继续对你的
code and when I mean when I say your
代码以及当我说您的意思时
code I don't mean just the step you
代码，我的意思并不只是你迈出的一步
wrote but also the libraries that you
还写了你的图书馆
rely on okay because I expect that most
依靠好的，因为我希望大多数
people will have to at least get the
人们至少必须得到
next version of their login utility or
他们的登录实用程序的下一版本或
framework etcetera modular application
框架等模块化应用
packaging remember that I said that
包装记得我说过
there's the J link that creates a
有一个J链接创建了一个
special runtime we have a tool that will
特殊的运行时，我们有一个工具
create a package so that it looks like a
创建一个程序包，使其看起来像一个
native application we have with JDK 8
JDK 8提供的本机应用程序
but it bundles the whole jury with JDK 9
但是它将整个评审团与JDK 9捆绑在一起
it uses this daily link tool to create a
它使用此每日链接工具来创建一个
smaller runtime just for your
更小的运行时间
application new version string have you
应用新版本的字符串有你吗
okay which version of Java is the
好的，哪个Java版本是
current one 8 update what 120 something
当前一8更新120什么
right and if you do a Java - version
正确，如果您使用Java版本
string what do you get one dot 8.0 you
字符串你会得到一个点8.0
something right what's that one dot
正确的一点是什么
what's that zero all of that there's
零是多少
very good reasons why those were there
这些东西在那里的很好的理由
to begin with
首先
but they're gone in JDK 9 so the version
但是它们在JDK 9中已经消失了，因此版本
string for 9 is 9 not 1.9 and it's got
9的字符串是9而不是1.9，它有
semantic versioning so there's no you
语义版本控制，所以没有你
know news and there is more than one
知道新闻，不止一个
digit to read so if you were parsing the
要读取的数字，如果您正在解析
version string we've seen code that
版本字符串，我们已经看到了代码
looks at the version string discards the
查看版本字符串将丢弃
first digit and starts looking at the
第一位数字，然后开始查看
second one that won't work ok
第二个行不通
ahead of time compilation if you don't
如果不提前编译
want to compile a winter Bureau on your
想在您的公司上编制冬季局
jet you want to create a compilation
您要创建编辑的喷气机
ahead of running available in the next
提前运行在下一个可用
one md5 string concatenation I love this
一个md5字符串串联我喜欢这个
one I had to you know look up what that
我不得不告诉你一个
meant as I mentioned we've introduced
就像我提到的，我们已经介绍了
invoke dynamic in 7 or 8 getting market
在7或8个越来越多的市场中调用动态
in 7 JDK 7 and this means that rather
在7 JDK 7中，这意味着
than the compiler figuring out the code
比编译器找出代码
it can say you know figure it out at
它可以说你知道在
runtime now what this will allow us to
现在运行时，这将使我们能够
do is anything compiled after we do this
做完之后要做的就是编译
right now we're the same but if we think
现在我们是一样的，但如果我们认为
of a better way of doing a string
做弦的更好方法
concatenation in the future
将来串联
we can make it so that code compiled
我们可以做到，这样代码可以编译
with 9 and above takes advantage of
9岁以上的人
those benefits you don't have to
这些不必要的好处
recompile it so this is what I call you
重新编译它，这就是我所说的
know housekeeping this is just looking
知道这只是看家务
forward when we come up with a better
当我们提出更好的建议时
idea
理念
you won't have to recompile to get that
您无需重新编译即可得到
advantage unified average collation
优势统一平均排序
login and we're switching the default
登录，我们切换默认
garbage collector okay now anybody here
垃圾收集器好吧，现在有人在这里
cares about which garbage collector in
关心哪个垃圾收集器
your application uses if you do I'm
您的应用程序使用的是
guessing that you have a parameter
猜你有一个参数
telling the operator the the runtime
告诉操作员运行时间
which one to use so you will not be
使用哪个，这样您就不会
affected these will only affect people
影响这些只会影响人
that don't specify a default okay
没有指定默认值就可以
project coin you're familiar with that
您熟悉的项目硬币
one came with JDK 7 we did some minor
JDK 7附带一个，我们做了一些小改动
changes to the language we're doing some
改变我们正在做的语言
further improvements ok
可以进一步改善
this one I like filter incoming
我喜欢这个过滤器传入
serialization data now this one I have
序列化数据现在这个我有
here because this one is actually now
在这里，因为这实际上是现在
available in versions 6 7 &amp; 8 so it's a
在版本6 7和8中可用，因此它是一个
mechanism by which you can tell don't
你可以告诉不要的机制
just accept any data here's a set of
只是接受任何数据，这是一组
rules my application only expect this
规则我的应用程序只期望这样
type of data to be serialize anything
要序列化的数据类型
else
其他
kick it out okay and this is as I said
踢出去好吧，这就是我说的
the only feature I can think of that's
我能想到的唯一特征是
started in 9 and has already been back
从9开始，已经回来了
board and it's available in current
板，目前可用
releases a bunch of garbage collection
释放一堆垃圾
combinations where deprecating in 8 can
在8个中可以弃用的组合
you tell which ones are red that's
你告诉那些是红色的
visible right so these guys right here
可见对，所以这些人就在这里
in red those were deprecated in JDK 8
红色表示在JDK 8中已弃用
and we have not been testing them so I
而且我们还没有测试它们，所以我
don't have the work probably well
工作做得不好
they're going to be gone in JDK 9 now
他们现在将在JDK 9中消失
what does that mean as a general rule if
这是什么一般规则
you're running your JDK now and you're
您现在正在运行JDK，并且您正在
getting warnings things like this thing
得到警告之类的东西
right if you set parmgen size in JDK 8
正确，如果您在JDK 8中设置了parmgen大小
it tells you I'm ignoring this I remove
它告诉你我忽略了我删除的内容
that you know this is this is we remove
您知道这是我们要删除的
this in JDK 8 in JDK 9 that same option
这在JDK 9中的JDK 8中是相同的选项
will error out so don't just ignore
会出错，所以不要只是忽略
those warnings they're there for a
这些警告，他们在那里
reason
原因
please and I know people are going to
请，我知道人们会
call me and complain about this when we
我们打电话给我抱怨
go live and I cherry-pick the ones I
上线，我挑我的那些
liked as I said there's about 90 of them
就像我说的那样，很喜欢
and there you can go and read about any
在那里您可以阅读任何内容
one of them in a lot more detail than
其中之一比
anybody you know could do in a single
您认识的任何人都可以一次完成
session okay
会议还可以
so now for my call to action download
现在就开始我的号召性用语下载
the JDK and early access build I think I
我认为我的JDK和早期访问版本
left it here just search for get ek9
留在这里只是搜索ek9
you'll find it we change the build
您会发现我们会更改版本
number periodically so don't just grab
定期编号，所以不要随便抓
one and test forever
一个，永远测试
you know check every time we've already
你知道我们每次都检查
reached feature complete so if you were
已完成功能，因此如果您
waiting for these to have all of the
等待这些拥有所有
features before you start a testing
开始测试之前的功能
you're not to wait anymore you can do it
您不再等待，您可以做到
today okay and there's a summary of
今天还可以，并且有一个摘要
changes on every build next one
在下一个版本上进行更改
join the conversation for every one of
参加每个人的对话
those jabs if you look for the
这些刺戳，如果您寻找
discussion field it'll tell you which
讨论区，它会告诉您
one of these areas you can ask questions
您可以问以下问题之一
about that people that know most about
关于最了解的人
these particular enhancements monitor
这些特定的增强监视器
their in those discussions you can go
他们在这些讨论中，你可以去
ahead join if you have any questions or
如有任何疑问，请提前加入
suggestions please review the archive
建议，请查看存档
because we've got lots of questions and
因为我们有很多问题，
nobody enjoys answering questions that
没有人喜欢回答这样的问题
were answered six months ago but if you
在六个月前得到了答复，但如果您
have any suggestions so you find any
有任何建议，所以你找到任何
problems you could ping me and then I
问题，你可以ping我，然后我
would pick them or you can just cut me
会选择他们，或者你可以砍我
out of the loop and go straight to them
跳出循环，直接去找他们
okay download some idea of your flavor
好吧，下载一些您的口味的想法
like your favorite might taste NetBeans
就像您喜欢的NetBeans一样
they offer now capabilities same thing
他们现在提供功能相同的东西
they're working to provide support for
他们正在努力为
the new features at GA like us they also
GA的新功能像我们一样，他们也
need feedback please get back to them
需要反馈请与他们联系
and tell them what they're doing right
告诉他们他们在做什么
and what they're doing wrong that Jade
以及他们在做什么翡翠
EPS tool that I mentioned it's available
我提到的EPS工具可用
in JDK 8 you're better off using the one
在JDK 8中，最好使用一个
in JDK 9 when you find something that
在JDK 9中，当您发现
you're not supposed to be using you'll
你不应该使用你会
actually tell you when we know which
告诉你什么时候知道
supported API you should be using
您应该使用的受支持的API
instead okay so please run that it'll
相反好吧，所以请运行它
make your transition to JDK 9 much
使您更轻松地过渡到JDK 9
simpler this is a little bit like
比较简单，这有点像
planning for retirement you do not want
不想退休
to wait until you have to go to JDK 9 to
等到您必须去JDK 9
do this if you do it now and do it
如果您现在就做就做
incrementally this will be easy
逐步地，这将很容易
and as I said there is this very
正如我所说的
convoluted set of here ad exports this
复杂的此处广告集导出
is what will allow you to we remove that
是什么让您我们将其删除
restriction and have those internal
限制，并有那些内部
api's reappear for your program okay so
api会重新出现在您的程序中，所以
that's it with the slide deck and I
滑盖就是这样，我
think we do have a few more minutes
认为我们还有几分钟
before I forget the guy that just came
在我忘记刚来的那个人之前
before we started Bruno reminded me to
在我们开始之前，布鲁诺提醒我
remind you that there is a reception
提醒您有招待会
we're going to have beer wine and that
我们要喝啤酒酒
kind of stuff where we had the food so
我们在这里吃东西的东西
after this session
会议结束后
don't just bowl to your cars you can
不要只是给你的车打碗
kill some time there and wait for the
在那消磨时间，等待
traffic to die and is there any
交通死了，有没有
questions from what I show or does
我所显示或所做的问题
anybody care to see a little demo of J
任何人都希望看到J的一些演示
shell and perhaps some sample code
外壳，也许还有一些示例代码
yeah let's let's try that and I haven't
是的，让我们尝试一下，我还没有
prayed to the demo gods so you're going
向演示之神祈祷，所以你要去
to have to bear with me my computer's
必须忍受我的电脑
also very slow can anybody read that
也很慢，有人可以读
first of all because this is not going
首先，因为这不会
to be fun can we change the resolution
为了好玩，我们可以改变分辨率
is that beatable yeah okay so this is
那是可击败的，是吗，所以这是
JDK 9 I think I'm a couple of versions
JDK 9我认为我有几个版本
back and as I said my computer super
回到我所说的我的电脑超级
slow here we go
慢点我们去
156 I'm going to show you J she'll
156我要告诉你她她会
remember that I mentioned that there is
记得我提到过
this tool the repple tool that will
这个工具repple工具
allow you to explore a little code so
让您探索一些代码，以便
one of my favorite here we go so haven't
我最喜欢的地方之一，我们去吧
done anything I can do simple things
做任何我可以做的简单的事情
like hello it's string right dot soup
像你好，这是串右点汤
I'm going to tap here and it tells me
我要点击这里，它告诉我
what are the methods that are available
有哪些可用的方法
for that string let's say substring now
对于那个字符串，让我们现在说子字符串
I'm going to do a shift tab and it tells
我要做一个制表符，它告诉
me what are the possible right methods
我有什么可能的正确方法
that I could be using there it's
我可能会在那里使用它
overloaded so it could be the beginning
超载，所以这可能是一个开始
the trend and I can say let's say from 2
趋势，我可以说2
to 4 and it creates this pseudo variable
到4并创建此伪变量
1 which is the 1 1 and also you can get
1就是1 1，你也可以得到
if you don't want have access to the IDE
如果您不想访问IDE
you can do this
你可以这样做
the example that I want to show is
我想展示的例子是
anybody ever try to compute the phases
任何人都试图计算相位
of the Moon right you want to know
你想知道的月亮
whether it's full moon or waxing moon or
无论是满月还是打蜡的月亮还是
wining moon etc etc you can do very
赢得月亮等你可以做得非常
complicated math to do it and I'm sure
要做复杂的数学运算，我敢肯定
somebody at NASA would love to tell you
NASA的某人很想告诉你
how to do it but I'm just going to cheat
怎么做，但我只是作弊
and I'm going to simply convert the date
我将简单地转换日期
that you want into a date in a lunar
您想要在农历中约会
calendar and the beauty of lunar
日历和农历之美
calendars is all of the months go
日历是所有月份
between one to either 29 or 30 and those
在1到29或30之间
dates match exactly the day of the moon
日期恰好符合月亮的日子
so that's all a blue right there is a
所以那都是蓝色的，有一个
calendar that supported here by default
默认情况下此处支持的日历
in JDK it's the historic calendar now
在JDK中，这是历史悠久的日历
it's where let's let's just do it again
在这里，让我们再做一次
I could type date dot time every single
我可以每个输入日期点时间
time but I could just do an import date
时间，但是我可以输入日期
time I'm sorry
时间我很抱歉
Java dot time here I'm going to need a
Java点时间在这里，我需要一个
couple of others let's get the time dot
其他几个让我们得到时间点
chrono and import any case you don't
计时并导入您没有的任何情况
remember Java that I can do the tap
记得我可以做水龙头的Java
thing and it will tell me so it's it's
东西，它会告诉我，就是这样
got the completion let's try this
完成了，让我们尝试一下
temporal chrono-field there so now if I
那里的时间时空，所以现在如果我
just wanted to get the current date I
只是想得到我的当前日期
can just they say something and say
他们可以说些什么吗？
local and I'm using that code completion
本地的，我正在使用该代码完成
because I just can type local date dot
因为我可以输入本地日期点
now that's a current date okay if I
现在这是当前日期，如果我
would like to know the same since I
我想知道一样
imported I'm going to show you by the
导入，我将向您展示
way list it is all that I've typed okay
方式列表就是我键入的所有内容
I can do a help if I want to know
我想知道的话可以帮忙
everything I can do but let's get the
我能做的一切，但让我们
current date in a lunar format and
以阴历格式显示的当前日期，以及
that's called cifra date dot now there
那现在叫做cifra日期点
I'm just going to look at the day Oh -
我只想看看那天-
since the moon starts at 0 0 new moon
因为月亮从0 0开始新月
we're pretty much new moon there is no
我们几乎是新月，没有
moon today out ok and you can do as you
今天好吧，你可以做你
can see pretty simple I don't have to go
可以看到很简单，我不必走
and write code that does it I didn't
并写出我没有做的代码
even put the semicolon I can do even the
甚至把分号都可以
dollar 6 it creates that variable for me
美元6会为我创建该变量
dot get
点得到
chrono-field dot
时空点
day of month there you go so you can see
一个月中的某天你可以去看看
here how can quickly do a function if I
如果我在这里如何快速执行功能
want to create a date rather than using
想要创建一个日期而不是使用
now I say local date dot and I can say
现在我说当地的日期点，我可以说
off and look it's a 2017 Oh 304 he'll
离开，然后看这是2017哦304他会
create dates like that so as you can see
这样创建日期，如您所见
creating new dates and times it's pretty
创建新的日期和时间很漂亮
straightforward that's one of the
直截了当的是
beauties of the new days hire 310 you
新的一天的美丽雇用310您
don't have to do the whole let me create
不必做全部让我创造
a calendar let me set the month and by
日历让我设定月份和
the way in this calendar January is one
这个日历一月的方式是
guess what January was in the previous
猜猜上一月是什么
calendar zero you know we're developers
日历零，您知道我们是开发人员
we start counting so current month went
我们开始计数，所以本月过去了
from zero to 11 go figure
从零到11
here's what it looks like my little
这就是我的小样子
completed class right here I'm going to
我要在这里完成课程
get the day form a year month day so if
从一年中的一个月日中获得一天，所以如果
I say okay here's a date from local
我说好，这是当地人的约会
daytime year-month-day this will accept
白天年月日这将接受
a year month day and it will return that
一年一个月的一天，它将返回
lunar day if you will okay now that
阴历日，如果你现在还可以的话
lunar day is based on a particular city
阴历日基于特定城市
on in the Middle East so it's not very
在中东，所以不是很
accurate but I'm just gonna you know
准确，但我会告诉你
fat-finger it and say okay if the value
胖手指，说好吧，如果值
is greater than four or less than twelve
大于四或小于十二
you're in the first quarter between 13
您处于第一季度的13
and 17 year on full moon between 18 and
和18岁至17岁之间的满月
26 you're in third quarter and
26您在第三季度
everything else that's one two three and
一二三的一切
27 to 30 that's New Moon okay now I
27到30就是新月了，现在我
could just run this but let's make it a
可以运行它，但让我们将其
little bit more interesting I would like
我想要一点点有趣
to put this in the my Oracle cloud
将此放入我的Oracle云
account because of course we have to put
帐户，因为我们当然要放
it in a cloud so that just means I have
它在云中，这意味着我有
to create a little function that reads
创建一个读取的小功能
write whatever you pass and spit it out
写下您通过的所有内容并将其吐出
so
所以
here it is I'm using spark to not have
这是我正在使用火花没有
to code anything of that because you
编码任何东西，因为你
know I'd not really want to go into the
知道我真的不想进入
nitty gritties of listening to a board I
听董事会的小气概我
I can pass the poll as a parameter if it
我可以将民意调查作为参数传递
doesn't work I'll use a DAT and here it
不起作用，我将使用DAT，在这里
says when I get a request just to check
说当我收到一个要求只是检查
that it's alive you know if I don't pass
你还活着，你知道我是否不通过
anything I'll reply with it's alive
我会回复的一切都还活着
and if I pass moon and I pass a
如果我通过月亮，我通过
parameter with date I can pass any date
带日期的参数我可以传递任何日期
and I'll just return the date and time
我将返回日期和时间
so here's this is I went to my Oracle
所以这是我去我的甲骨文
application cloud and I just loaded this
应用程序云，我刚刚加载了这个
thing now here's the exact same can you
现在事情完全一样，你能
read that can I write and just to see
阅读我可以写的只是看
that I'm not cheating and adjusting in
我没有作弊和适应
hard code a couple of them here's the
硬编码其中的几个是
moon phases for here California in 2017
2017年加利福尼亚州的月相
and I just Google this one right so
我只是谷歌这个权利，所以
let's try full moon October 5 of 2017 so
让我们尝试2017年10月5日的满月吧
what we're going to say is
我们要说的是
there you go full moon you want to try
你去那里满月你想尝试
first quarter let's say April 3rd
假设第一季度是4月3日
aygul so it's up and running working
Aygul，所以它已经启动并正在运行
literally about here this is it
从字面上看这就是它
including the part where I listen to the
包括我听的部分
poor word and do everything so pretty
不好的话，做的一切都那么漂亮
straightforward please give it a try and
简单明了，请尝试一下
you know as you can see this is I had
你知道，你可以看到这是我
already logged in I can show you a
已经登录，我可以告诉你
little bit about the project just
关于项目的一点点
because all of your developers so it
因为您所有的开发人员都这样
just requires there's a little tool here
只需要这里有一个小工具
that will grab all of the dependencies
它将抓住所有依赖
put it in a single jar file include a
将其放在一个jar文件中，包括
little file that says how do I want to
小文件说我要
run it command Java - jar this is the
运行它命令Java-jar，这是
name of the project right this is the
这个项目的名称是
jar puts all of this into that zip file
jar将所有这些内容放入该zip文件中
and literally to run this in the Oracle
并从字面上在Oracle中运行
cloud all I had to do was upload that
我要做的就是上传
zip file and this is what you have
压缩文件，这就是你所拥有的
running here so if you have more
在这里跑，所以如果你有更多
questions about this particular part
有关此特定部分的问题
about putting it on the cloud there's a
关于将它放在云上有一个
guy called Shawn Smith on the room right
在房间右边叫肖恩·史密斯的家伙
next door to this one that will be
隔壁的这将是
probably having beers in the next few
在接下来的几周里可能会有啤酒
minutes on the next session I can point
我可以指出的下一次会议记录
them to you if you want that's it thank
他们给你，如果你想要的就是这样谢谢
you for coming
你来了
if you have a questions right
如果您有问题的权利
okay what's the module and the module
好的，什么是模块和模块
system sure okay so the idea of the
系统肯定可以，所以
module system as I said is instead of
我说的是模块系统，而不是
having one monolithic project for run
有一个整体项目要运行
the JDK we've separated the libraries
在JDK中，我们分离了库
into different modules now what does
现在分成不同的模块
this mean to you in practice if you do
在实践中，这对您意味着
not care for modules it means nothing
不在乎模块，这没什么意思
right so your programs will continue to
对，这样您的程序将继续
run you do not have to switch to a
运行您不必切换到
module system right everything they did
模块系统对他们所做的一切
it before will continue to work so it
它会继续工作，所以它
will impact us at the JDK level except
将在JDK级别影响我们，除了
for the fact that if you were using
因为如果您使用
internal API a side-effect is their
内部API的副作用是
healing now because of the module system
现在由于模块系统而恢复
right and as I said that could probably
对，正如我所说，这可能
be a full one-hour session right at a
在一个完整的一小时的会议上
high level is we've grouped a collection
高层是我们对集合进行了分组
of api's if you think of a bunch of
如果想起一堆
packages all of the ones that have to do
打包所有必须要做的
with security into one module whole ones
安全地集成到一个模块中
have to do for managing the desktop into
必须将桌面管理到
one module it's it's a different it's
一个模块是不同的
it's it as I said it's a collection of
就像我说的是它的集合
api's it's built into every module that
api是内置于每个模块中的
has some dependencies to every to two
每两个都有一些依赖
different modules as I should probably
我可能应该使用不同的模块
show you the module system image
向您展示模块系统映像
[Music]
[音乐]
right so we have modularized the JDK us
对，所以我们已经将JDK模块化了
a developer can mimic that and do that
开发人员可以模仿并做到这一点
to your own code and separate your code
到您自己的代码并分离您的代码
instead of just having you know the
而不只是让你知道
package level you can have different
套餐级别可以有不同
modules and the idea is that modules
模块的想法是
will be self-contained
将是独立的
they will only you know they'll create a
他们只会让你知道他们会创建一个
dependency graph so it'll be easy to
依赖图，因此很容易
update on module at a time now you don't
现在一次不更新模块
have to do any of this but you could
必须做任何事情，但是你可以
right my point is as I said yeah you
是的，我的意思是我说的是
could say the JDK before was one
可以说以前的JDK是一个
gigantic module right you if you didn't
巨大的模块适合您，如果您没有
want to exclude any module you're pretty
想排除任何你漂亮的模块
much in the same place where you were
和你以前在同一个地方
before I said okay let me put a pin on
在我说好之前，让我别针
that one come up here because as I said
那个人来这里是因为我说过
we can spend a lot more than five
我们可以花超过五倍的钱
minutes that's not a three minute
分钟不是三分钟
conversation that's more like a thirty
对话更像是三十
minute conversation and I'll be happy to
分钟的交谈，我很乐意
have it right here right now just not
现在就在这里
with everybody else here okay so see you
和其他人在这里好吧，再见
guys at the refreshment table
茶点桌上的家伙